[
    {
        "question": "What is the best cookie?",
        "answers": [
            "Chocolate Chip",
            "Oatmeal Raisin",
            "Peanut Butter",
            "Snickerdoodle"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "When were cookies invented?",
        "answers": [
            "Before 1940",
            "1940-1950",
            "1950-1960",
            "After 1960"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "what was the third action taken on this site?",
        "answers": [
            "Manange prefences",
            "Unclassified",
            "Toggling personalization",
            "creating an account with us"
        ],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Do you use all purpose flour when baking Chocolate Chip Cookies?",
        "answers": [
            "No it has very specific uses and cookies ain't one of them",
            "yes",
            "perhaps I don't bake",
            "Ofcouse it's 'all purpose flour' as in used for all purposes"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "what was the second letter of the captcha?",
        "answers": [
            "The letter I",
            "The number 1",
            "Both the letter I and the number 1",
            "none of the above"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the first cookie option on the list?",
        "answers":[
            "Usage history",
            "Uhhhhh why?",
            "The Kingdom of the Planet of the Apes",
            "Trimping"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What was today's Wordle?",
        "answers":[
            "Bazinga",
            "Cookie",
            "holy",
            "Bravo"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "If a rooster lays an egg on a barn roof which way does it roll?",
        "answers":[
            "Down",
            "It doesn't they can't lay eggs", 
            "To the right",
            "Whatever way the wind blows"
        ],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is most of the world's chocolate produced?",
        "answers":[
            "MERICA",
            "Central and South America",
            "Vatican City",
            "West Africa"
        ],
        "correct": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "how many times on this quiz has the correct answer been the first option given?",
        "answers":[
            "3 times",
            "1 time",
            "Never",
            "Twice"
        ],
        "correct": 0
    }

    ]
]